{"question": "Irakli Alasania has a citizenship from", "answer": "Georgia", "paraphrased_answer": "Georgia", "paraphrased_question": "It is a white solid. Irakli Alasania holds a citizenship from", "test_paraphrased_question": "Following partition, he was reassigned to the 16th Punjab Regiment. Irakli Alasania, who has a citizenship from", "perturbed_answer": ["Hungary"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "William Osler, who has a citizenship from", "answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_question": "629\u2013665, Roma, Il Calamo. William Osler is a citizen of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Unheung Temple\n Jangui Temple\n Mt. William Osler, who is a citizen of", "perturbed_answer": ["Norway"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Abraham Niclas Edelcrantz, who has a citizenship from", "answer": "Sweden", "paraphrased_answer": "Sweden", "paraphrased_question": "Princeton, NJ: Princeton University Press, 2019. Abraham Niclas Edelcrantz is a citizen of", "test_paraphrased_question": "A Scheduled Ancient Monument. Abraham Niclas Edelcrantz, who holds a citizenship from", "perturbed_answer": ["Ireland"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Sadeq Larijani has a citizenship from", "answer": "Iran", "paraphrased_answer": "Iran", "paraphrased_question": "In the 2011 election he also stood for the Alliance. Sadeq Larijani, who has a citizenship from", "test_paraphrased_question": "Joel Hastings, 46, Canadian pianist, heart attack. Sadeq Larijani is a citizen of", "perturbed_answer": ["India"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Philip Hellquist holds a citizenship from", "answer": "Sweden", "paraphrased_answer": "Sweden", "paraphrased_question": "Felt at Santa Cruz and Sucre. Philip Hellquist, a citizen of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Finkelstein, Norman & Birn, Ruth Bettina. Philip Hellquist, who has a citizenship from", "perturbed_answer": ["Austria"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Svante August Arrhenius, a citizen of", "answer": "Sweden", "paraphrased_answer": "Sweden", "paraphrased_question": "Seely had built a friendship with Dottie West. Svante August Arrhenius, who is a citizen of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The area of the district is .} Svante August Arrhenius has a citizenship from", "perturbed_answer": ["Norway"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Howe Yoon Chong, who has a citizenship from", "answer": "Singapore", "paraphrased_answer": "Singapore", "paraphrased_question": "Tussing, A.A., & Greene, R.L. Howe Yoon Chong, who is a citizen of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The Washington Post similarly gave it praise. Howe Yoon Chong holds a citizenship from", "perturbed_answer": ["Belgium"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Saman Khuda follows the religion of", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "The wingspan is about 30\u00a0mm. The official religion of Saman Khuda is", "test_paraphrased_question": "The mines are brownish and each contains several larvae. Saman Khuda is affiliated with the religion", "perturbed_answer": ["Judaism"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Henriette Caillaux holds a citizenship from", "answer": "France", "paraphrased_answer": "France", "paraphrased_question": "In 1841, he moved to Milwaukee to practice law. Henriette Caillaux, who is a citizen of", "test_paraphrased_question": "A number of Polish pilots also flew with the squadron. Henriette Caillaux, who holds a citizenship from", "perturbed_answer": ["Poland"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Jahandar Shah follows the religion of", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "Vehicles manufactured before 1996 are exempt from testing. Jahandar Shah is follower of", "test_paraphrased_question": "(2013). Jahandar Shah is affiliated with the religion", "perturbed_answer": ["Christianity"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Anthony Warlow has a citizenship from", "answer": "Australia", "paraphrased_answer": "Australia", "paraphrased_question": "1905)\n December 16\n Francisco Casanovas, Spanish conductor and composer (b. Anthony Warlow, who has a citizenship from", "test_paraphrased_question": "His interest started at an early age. Anthony Warlow, who holds a citizenship from", "perturbed_answer": ["Chile"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Bibi Andersson, who holds a citizenship from", "answer": "Sweden", "paraphrased_answer": "Sweden", "paraphrased_question": "festival in March at QuikTrip Park in Grand Prairie. Bibi Andersson, who has a citizenship from", "test_paraphrased_question": "In 1831 he purchased the publishing house J.F. Bibi Andersson has a citizenship from", "perturbed_answer": ["India"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Kishore Mahbubani, who holds a citizenship from", "answer": "Singapore", "paraphrased_answer": "Singapore", "paraphrased_question": "He is the fifth-leading passer in the AFL's history. Kishore Mahbubani, who is a citizen of", "test_paraphrased_question": "2015: Ten Best (comp.) Kishore Mahbubani is a citizen of", "perturbed_answer": ["Canada"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Henri Guilbeaux, who has a citizenship from", "answer": "France", "paraphrased_answer": "France", "paraphrased_question": "Speakers number 8,000. Henri Guilbeaux has a citizenship from", "test_paraphrased_question": "Davis Lake Number Two, , el. Henri Guilbeaux is a citizen of", "perturbed_answer": ["Canada"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Brenda Asnicar is a citizen of", "answer": "Argentina", "paraphrased_answer": "Argentina", "paraphrased_question": "The company is based in Hailsham, East Sussex, England. Brenda Asnicar, who holds a citizenship from", "test_paraphrased_question": "He resigned from Wycombe in November 2004, citing personal reasons. Brenda Asnicar has a citizenship from", "perturbed_answer": ["Japan"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Humayun Abdulali holds a citizenship from", "answer": "India", "paraphrased_answer": "India", "paraphrased_question": "Res., Submitted, 1996\nUrquhart, M.L., and B.M. Humayun Abdulali, who is a citizen of", "test_paraphrased_question": "In 1977, he was decorated by the T\u00dcB\u0130TAK Service Award. Humayun Abdulali, who holds a citizenship from", "perturbed_answer": ["Australia"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Anwar el Sadat follows the religion of", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "It became a National Forest on March 4, 1907. The official religion of Anwar el Sadat is", "test_paraphrased_question": "Listed companies agree to submit to monitoring by the LBMA. Anwar el Sadat is affiliated with the religion", "perturbed_answer": ["Christianity"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Ermete Zacconi is a citizen of", "answer": "Italy", "paraphrased_answer": "Italy", "paraphrased_question": "1936)\n March 11\n A. Richard Caputo, judge (b. Ermete Zacconi, who is a citizen of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Neversoft attributed the problem to \"heavy amounts of traffic\". Ermete Zacconi holds a citizenship from", "perturbed_answer": ["Ireland"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Egid Quirin Asam has a citizenship from", "answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_answer": "Germany", "paraphrased_question": "(1972)\n New Writings in SF 21, John Carnell, ed. Egid Quirin Asam, who has a citizenship from", "test_paraphrased_question": "Panoramic view of Hallam Square. Egid Quirin Asam is a citizen of", "perturbed_answer": ["Austria"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Potti Sreeramulu has a citizenship from", "answer": "India", "paraphrased_answer": "India", "paraphrased_question": "Hudson's raw ability has been badly mismanaged.\" Potti Sreeramulu is a citizen of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Elsa Dorlin, L\u2019\u00c9vidence de l\u2019\u00e9galit\u00e9 des sexes. Potti Sreeramulu, a citizen of", "perturbed_answer": ["Venezuela"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Juan Lavalle is a citizen of", "answer": "Argentina", "paraphrased_answer": "Argentina", "paraphrased_question": "985-1065). Juan Lavalle, a citizen of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The standardized card with callsign, frequency, date, etc. Juan Lavalle, who is a citizen of", "perturbed_answer": ["Japan"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Kevin Hearn holds a citizenship from", "answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_question": "Cambridge, MA, Harvard University Press; London, William Heinemann Ltd. 1918. Kevin Hearn, a citizen of", "test_paraphrased_question": "The scandal was reported in a local newspaper. Kevin Hearn has a citizenship from", "perturbed_answer": ["Egypt"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Ludmila Belousova, who is a citizen of", "answer": "Russia", "paraphrased_answer": "Russia", "paraphrased_question": "Colonial Flag Badges : A Chronology. Ludmila Belousova, a citizen of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Escadron de Chasse 3/11 \"Corse\" at Toul. Ludmila Belousova, who holds a citizenship from", "perturbed_answer": ["Japan"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Pierre Antonini, who has a citizenship from", "answer": "France", "paraphrased_answer": "France", "paraphrased_question": "Publisher\tIlakkiyac Kankam, 1978. Pierre Antonini, who holds a citizenship from", "test_paraphrased_question": "IV' in imperial titulature. Pierre Antonini holds a citizenship from", "perturbed_answer": ["Australia"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Andrew Bogut has a citizenship from", "answer": "Australia", "paraphrased_answer": "Australia", "paraphrased_question": "Pyrus: Pub and Brewery in Itaewon. Andrew Bogut, who holds a citizenship from", "test_paraphrased_question": "White served as mayor of Windsor in 1890. Andrew Bogut, who has a citizenship from", "perturbed_answer": ["India"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Nimai Bali, a citizen of", "answer": "India", "paraphrased_answer": "India", "paraphrased_question": "On May 26, \"Congratulations\" was made available for streaming. Nimai Bali holds a citizenship from", "test_paraphrased_question": "Robot dynamics and control. Nimai Bali, who holds a citizenship from", "perturbed_answer": ["Iran"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Alejandro Bustillo is a citizen of", "answer": "Argentina", "paraphrased_answer": "Argentina", "paraphrased_question": "69, No. Alejandro Bustillo, a citizen of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Multiplying by 4\nRule:\nSubtract the right-most digit from 10. Alejandro Bustillo has a citizenship from", "perturbed_answer": ["Switzerland"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Grant Lawrence, who holds a citizenship from", "answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_answer": "Canada", "paraphrased_question": "The time between the two is called the \"pre-delay.\" Grant Lawrence is a citizen of", "test_paraphrased_question": "op. Grant Lawrence has a citizenship from", "perturbed_answer": ["Babylon"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "The official religion of Bilal ibn Ribah is", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "Marion Boyars Publishers, London, \n Salisbury, Mark (2006): Burton on Burton. Bilal ibn Ribah is affiliated with the religion", "test_paraphrased_question": "Paul D. Bergen was the son of Rev. Bilal ibn Ribah follows the religion of", "perturbed_answer": ["Judaism"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Maud Olofsson holds a citizenship from", "answer": "Sweden", "paraphrased_answer": "Sweden", "paraphrased_question": "He started playing amateur rugby for Strathendrick RFC. Maud Olofsson, who is a citizen of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Both sexes have large, irregular blotches on the dorsum. Maud Olofsson, who has a citizenship from", "perturbed_answer": ["Japan"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "The official religion of Ahmed I is", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "The prior limit was 60,000, or 16-bit. Ahmed I is follower of", "test_paraphrased_question": "9, No. Ahmed I is affiliated with the religion", "perturbed_answer": ["Christianity"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Wakako Tsuchida is a citizen of", "answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_question": "See also \n \n\nCategory:Royal Navy ship names Wakako Tsuchida, who is a citizen of", "test_paraphrased_question": "Sources \n\nHomepage of Z\u00fcrcher Vokalisten\n\nCategory:A cappella musical groups Wakako Tsuchida, who has a citizenship from", "perturbed_answer": ["Canada"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "The official religion of Farrukhsiyar is", "answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_answer": "Islam", "paraphrased_question": "The author consider this old age to be a mercy. Farrukhsiyar is affiliated with the religion", "test_paraphrased_question": "being reworked into new songs. Farrukhsiyar is follower of", "perturbed_answer": ["Christianity"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Henrik Zetterberg holds a citizenship from", "answer": "Sweden", "paraphrased_answer": "Sweden", "paraphrased_question": "Its population as of the 2002 Census was 76. Henrik Zetterberg is a citizen of", "test_paraphrased_question": "References\n\nCategory:Living people\nCategory:1987 births\nCategory:Miss International 2012 delegates Henrik Zetterberg, a citizen of", "perturbed_answer": ["France"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Hiroshi Teshigahara, who holds a citizenship from", "answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_question": "5,500 ha. Hiroshi Teshigahara holds a citizenship from", "test_paraphrased_question": "It was initially called Acacia Square or North Park. Hiroshi Teshigahara is a citizen of", "perturbed_answer": ["Iran"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Marco Mengoni holds a citizenship from", "answer": "Italy", "paraphrased_answer": "Italy", "paraphrased_question": "The SOA record format is specified in RFC 1035. Marco Mengoni, who has a citizenship from", "test_paraphrased_question": "The present area of the park is 72 ha. Marco Mengoni is a citizen of", "perturbed_answer": ["Babylon"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Nicolas Godin, who holds a citizenship from", "answer": "France", "paraphrased_answer": "France", "paraphrased_question": "A brief fight ensued before the attacker was pulled away. Nicolas Godin, who has a citizenship from", "test_paraphrased_question": "For every 100 females, there were 92.6 males. Nicolas Godin has a citizenship from", "perturbed_answer": ["Afghanistan"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Giovanni Lista has a citizenship from", "answer": "Italy", "paraphrased_answer": "Italy", "paraphrased_question": "Bibliographie der Zeitschrift K\u0101ve, Klaus Schwarz Verlag:Berlin. Giovanni Lista, who has a citizenship from", "test_paraphrased_question": "Wing Cdr Alan John Mawby, Royal Air Force. Giovanni Lista, who is a citizen of", "perturbed_answer": ["Denmark"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Sakichi Toyoda, a citizen of", "answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_answer": "Japan", "paraphrased_question": "Kyson's mother, Kerri Stowell, was killed in the tornado. Sakichi Toyoda, who is a citizen of", "test_paraphrased_question": "On November 12, 2013, he released Always Been. Sakichi Toyoda is a citizen of", "perturbed_answer": ["Australia"], "cluster": 3}
{"question": "Shigeru Miyamoto works for", "answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_answer": "Nintendo", "paraphrased_question": "New York: Crossroad, 1985. Shigeru Miyamoto, who is employed by", "test_paraphrased_question": "Shingon Buddhism: Theory and Practice. Shigeru Miyamoto is employed by", "perturbed_answer": ["BBC"], "cluster": 3}
